Let's split up.
Ningning,
you go to the bar.
Okay.
Be careful.
Shi'an,
come with me to the dance floor.
Okay.
Are you okay?
You have a murderous look in your eyes.
You don't look like you're here for fun at all.
Do you love me or not?
I love you.
Push me.
You're so pretty, miss.
Name your price.
Be with me tonight.
You brat, how dare you steal my girl?
I think you have a death wish.
Using a gun with your left hand.
Are you stupid?
Zheng Kun,
I have your special dumdum bullets.
You can't escape.
Don't come any closer!
If you come closer, I'll kill her!
If I take you back to the police station,
I'm afraid you won't be able to keep this job.
Please don't.
Officer, you know,
what we dancers fear most is
getting involved with the police.
Then I can give you one more chance.
Answer whatever I ask.
Okay.
Do you know that Zheng Kun killed someone?
No, no, no.
I've only known him for a month.
I don't even know what he does.
Then what kind of people does he usually contact,
and where does he live?
He would never tell me that.
Usually, whenever we talk about him,
he stops immediately.
But he spends money quite generously on me,
so I never cared.
Has he been acting strange lately?
Recently,
he's been really good in bed.
Be specific.
He looks strong,
but
he's not very good at that.
He said he got hurt in a fight before.
But
the night before yesterday,
he took a strange pill.
He suddenly became a different person,
extremely excited,
and
he kept going all night.
Do you still have that pill?
No, no, no.
No, no.
I mean,
I need to test that pill.
Just to take a look.
When he wants to do that,
he brings it,
and only enough for the day.
He won't let me touch it.
He even threw away the wrapper later.
The wrapper of that pill is quite unique.
It has a colorful snake on it.
Is this it?
Yes, that's it.
Professor Bai, you are well-versed in both Chinese and Western cultures.
You must know what this drawing is about.
Snakes represent demons in Western culture.
What about a colorful snake like this?
Is it possible
that it's a symbol?
I really don't know what it means.
Give me some time to study it carefully.
Okay.
Thank you, Professor Bai.
What's wrapped in the colorful banded krait is a special aphrodisiac.
The person using the special aphrodisiac actually has special dumdum bullets.
I think it looks like a totem.
I don't think this pattern has any deep meaning.
Maybe it's just a trademark.
Zheng Kun must have taken some kind of aphrodisiac.
And it must be a smuggled banned drug.
As long as we find this drug,
we will naturally know everything.
It's a pity Zheng Kun got away.
Inspector Jiang.
What?
Are these your new underlings?
These are my junior brother and sister.
One is good at chemistry,
and the other is good at kung fu.
I brought them here to learn.
This is Mr. Wang, the forensic doctor.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
You know chemistry?
I study a bit of industrial chemistry.
Just the basics.
Come here.
Come help me take a look.
Take a look.
Look at what?
Mr. Wang, stop studying it.
Didn't you say a body
was sent over in the middle of the night?
Yes.
This way.
Here.
Come.
Zheng Kun.
Iron Sand Palm.
This is Zheng Kun's autopsy report.
The fatal wound
is the Iron Sand Palm strike on his chest.
Nowadays in this city,
there aren't many people who know martial arts.
Who did you think of?
The Jiuhe Gang
started out by practicing martial arts.
Any other discoveries?
In Zheng Kun's blood,
we found ayahuasca.
Ayahuasca is a banned drug.
It has severe hallucinogenic effects.
It is not produced
domestically.
Why would it appear here?
It must have been smuggled in.
It's the Jiuhe Gang.
Among a batch of banned drugs we seized last year,
there was ayahuasca.
Then it seems the Jiuhe Gang is a major suspect.
Then what role did Zheng Kun play?
He was in charge of transport.
He stole and used some himself.
After we found out, he was silenced.
As long as we find out where Zheng Kun went,
we can find this batch of banned drugs.
Then let's split up.
Talcum powder,
coffee beans,
they were all used to cover up the banned drugs,
frame Hengtong Company,
and cause my father's death.
Lei Lie, I won't let you off.
Huo Qishan of the Huo family
pays his respects to Great-Aunt.
[Net]
Great-Aunt, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Just a scratch.
Did you hear that?
Li Chengrui,
our Great-Aunt
is the apple of the eye
of everyone in the Huo family.
If anything happens to her,
believe it or not, I'll shoot you.
Yes.
Go, go, go.
Good grandson, you came just in time.
Tell me nicely,
between the mayor,
the police superintendent,
and you, who is more powerful?
If you put it that way,
it must be the mayor.
But,
he
has no military power,
only administrative power.
When he usually sees me,
he has to respectfully call me
Lord Huo.
He
is just a corrupt official who spends his time drinking and womanizing.
In the Phoenix City area,
the Huo family calls the shots.
Isn't this Great-Aunt
Lord Huo's daughter?
In this Phoenix City,
the Huo family's century-old foundation
relies on
their own Taoist sect.
Huo Yining
is the leader chosen by the Huo family through divination.
Lord Huo, I want to ask you about someone.
Lei Lie, the leader of the Jiuhe Gang,
do you know him?
I know him,
but we're not close.
It's nothing.
I just overturned the Jiuhe Gang's lair a few days ago,
so I'm just asking casually.
You should have overturned it.
Adjutant Zhang has arrived.
On behalf of Lord Huo, presenting a Ruyi
and a pair of South Sea coral screens.
Ruyi,
South Sea coral.
Not close.